[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "state": "latinx",
    "question": "Are you Hispanic, LatinX, or Spanish (if so what ethnic group do you identify with)?",
    "detail": "You may say yes to more than one",
    "answers": "LATINX"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "state": "race",
    "question": "What is your race?",
    "detail": "One or more categories may be selected",
    "multiple": true,
    "answers": "RACE"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "state": "gender",
    "question": "Do you consider youself to be?",
    "answers": "GENDER"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "state": "sexual_orientation",
    "question": "Which of the following do you consider yourself to be?",
    "answers": "ORIENTATION"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "state": "living_situation",
    "question": "Describe where you live?",
    "answers": "HOUSING"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "state": "college_enrolled",
    "question": "Are you currently attending college?",
    "answers": "YES_NO"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "state": "employment_status",
    "question": "What is your current employment status?",
    "answers": "EMPLOYMENT"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "state": "military_service",
    "question": "Have you ever served in the Armed Forces, the Reserves, or the National Guard?",
    "answers": "YES_NO"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "state": "arrested_in_last_month",
    "number_input": true,
    "question": "In the past 30 days, how many times have you been arrested?"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "state": "parole_or_probation",
    "question": "Are you on parole or probation?",
    "answers": "YES_NO"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "state": "informed_of_HIV_status",
    "question": "Have you ever been informed of your HIV status (this is, whether or not you are HIV-positive) based on the result of an HIV test?",
    "answers": "YES_NO"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "state": "informed_of_VH_status",
    "question": "Have you ever been informed of your viral hepatitis (VH) status (this is, whether or not you are infected with a hepitatis virus) based on the result of a VH test?",
    "answers": "YES_NO"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "state": "knowledge_of_SUD_healthcare_treatment",
    "question": "Would you know where to go near where you live to see a health care professional regarding a drug or alcohol problem?",
    "answers": "YES_NO"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "state": "knowledge_of_HIV_STD_healthcare_treatment",
    "question": "Would you know where to go near where you live to see a healthcare professional regarding HIV/AIDS or other sexually transmitted health issues?",
    "answers": "YES_NO"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "state": "pretax_household_income",
    "question": "How much income have you and your family members made in the last year before taxes?",
    "detail": "Include child support and cash payments from the government - for example wellface [TANF], SSI, or unemployment compensation.",
    "answers": "INCOME"
  }
]
